Hadi Banaei

210-646-4747

hadi_banaei1976@yahoo.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/hadi-banaei-779b4372/

Hadibanaei25@gmail.com

*US Citizen authorized to work for any employer and willing to relocate

OBJECTIVE

Exceptionally well organized, flexible and resourceful IT Specialist with more than 15 years of experience and is a firm believer in teamwork and collaboration to achieve common goals, striving to improve the overall work situation. Looking for a position in your organization where I can utilize my skills and experience to manage, maintain and maximize your network capabilities.

EDUCATION / CERTIFICATE

Master of Computer Engineering (Software orientation), PNU University, Iran Bachelor of Industrial Engineering (System analysis orientation), Azad University, Iran

- Microsoft Certified IT professional (MCITP)
- Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP)
- Microsoft Certified Technology Specialist (MCTS)
- Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA)
- Microsoft Certified Solutions Expert (MCSE)
- A+ certificate

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

IT Manager for Orono Pharmacy in Orono, ME. since 2011 to present time

ICHTO (Iranian Cultural Heritage, Handicrafts and Tourism Organization), Iran

IT Manager on launching a Performance Based Budgeting System Project

2016-2019

- Set up subsystem service cost
- Approve the actions of each department separately
- Check the rate of each action and program

Director of ICT Center

2015-2016

- Responsible for more than 800 clients and servers.
- Review and approve the process of corporate services (B2B, B2C, G2G, G2B, G2C, ...)

Deputy Director of ICT Center

2014-2015

- Responsible for more than 800 clients and servers.
- Revision of the structure and organization chart of the organization
- Review and approve the process of corporate services (B2B, B2C, G2G, G2B, G2C, ...)
- Review and technical action to select the integrated administrative and financial software system

IT Manager for Handicraft Dept.

2010-2014

- Responsible for more than 80 clients and servers.
- Maintenance and development of hardware and software local area network deployments for computers, servers and printers.
- Setup an active directory server

IT Manager at Sa'd Abad Museum Palace

2005-2010

- Responsible for more than 150 clients and servers.
- Maintenance and development of hardware and software local area network deployments for computers, servers and printers
- Fiber Optic Network Project Supervisor
- Set up and maintain a CCTV system inside the office and set up by IP cameras.

240 646 4747